lifepositive.com 2016-02-23

# Privacy Policy - Life Positive

This statement discloses the privacy practices for Lifepositive.com on the Internet. For further information please also consult our online Help Center, where you can view the Terms and Conditions of Service Agreement.

Lifepositive.com has adopted a set of information management guidelines which serve as the basis for our customer and advertiser relationships. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page and will be effective immediately.

Lifepositive.com is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Web sites to which it may link.

**What information does Lifepositive.com gather/track about you?**

**Registration:**  During a free registration process prior to using the site, Lifepositive.com requires that you supply a unique subscriber ID, e-mail address, and demographic information (country, zip code, age and sex are required; household income is optional). Subscribers must agree to the terms of our Terms and Conditions of Service Agreement. On occasion, Lifepositive.com also collects additional personal information from subscribers in connection with optional contests, surveys, or special offers.

**Content of other sites :  **Lifepositive.com is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Web sites to which it may link.

**Premium Services:  **Our site may have premium areas, available to our subscribers by payment. In this case, our site will use a third-party E-Commerce network to process payments. This E-Commerce network will collect and store credit card and other information to bill the subscriber for these optional premium services. By purchasing in our Lifepositive.com Subscription Services area or our Kiosk area, you agree that Lifepositive.com may store information you provide as part of the purchasing process.

**Cookies:**  Lifepositive.com employs cookies to recognize you and your access privileges on Lifepositive.com, as well as to track site usage. Subscribers who do not accept cookies from the domain Lifepositive.com may not be able to access some areas of the Lifepositive.com site.

**IP Addresses:**  Lifepositive.com also logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We do not use IP address logs to track your session or your behavior on our site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**What does Lifepositive.com do with the information it gathers/tracks?**

**Statistical Analysis and Banner Advertising** : Lifepositive.com may perform statistical analysis of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site (for product development purposes) and to inform advertisers as to how many consumers have seen or “clicked” their advertising banners. Lifepositive.com also uses demographic and preference information to allow advertising banners on our Web site to be targeted, in aggregate, to the readers for whom they are most pertinent. This means that readers see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer’s experience and the effectiveness of the ads. In this statistical analysis and banner advertisement targeting, we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form.  **Personal information about you as an individual subscriber will not be provided to any third party without your consent.**

**E-Mail:**  Using the e-mail addresses provided at registration, Lifepositive.com periodically sends promotional e-mail to its subscribers about services offered by Lifepositive.com. Lifepositive.com may contact you regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement, and to confirm registration.

**Data Security:**  To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. Visit our E-Commerce Network Provider for information about the security procedures used to protect your credit card information submitted to Lifepositive.com Online Subscriptions and Kiosk purchases.

**With whom does Lifepositive.com share the information it gathers/tracks?**

Lifepositive.com shares the information it gathers, in aggregate form, with advertisers and other partners.  **We do not release personal information about you as an individual to third parties.**  Lifepositive.com will provide you all of your information provided at registration [upon request](mailto:wecare@lifepositive.net). This information will only be sent to the e-mail address on file for the subscriber ID associated with it.

**LPMail:**  During the registration process, new users who select to register for LPMail become LPMail members. If you select this option, LPMail will use the information collected on the LPMail/Lifepositive.com registration form to provide targeted e-mails to you on behalf of advertisers. You will only receive e-mail message from LPMail if you elect this opt-in service. Lifepositive.com may use this information as set forth in this privacy policy.

**MERCHANDISE SALES:  **Lifepositive.com uses a third party E – Commerce network to process online purchases. Magazine subscriptions and other merchandise will be available in the Lifepositive.com Bazaar where you can visit kiosks and shops provided by Lifepositive.com and other vendors.

**Forums:**  Lifepositive.com offers forums, chat and online message boards. Any information you disclose when posting a message in these Forums becomes public. Moreover, subscribers who post a message in our Forums make their e-mail addresses available to others through a feature of our Forums software, which could result in unsolicited e-mail from other subscribers or parties. For more information about Forums see the terms and conditions of service or write to the Forums moderator at [ **wecare@lifepositive.net**](mailto:wecare@lifepositive.net).

**Opting-Out, Corrections and Cancellations**

Upon request, Lifepositive.com will a) Remove you and your personal information, from our database, thereby canceling your registration; b) Correct personal information that you state is erroneous; or c) Permit you to “opt out” of further e-mail contact (excepting notification of major changes to the service) while still allowing access to the site. To request a correction or cancellation, enter lifepositive.com and visit our help center or send e-mail to [Customer Service](mailto:wecare@lifepositive.net).
